Today, we're making a drawer handle out of bone.
We just put the drill bit in and drill the hole in the center of the first hole that we were attempting to make.
I'm going to take the polishing bit.
And I'm going to actually make the hole big enough that I can cut down farther in with my grinding bit.
We're not gonna--we don't need to go all the way through with either one.
So, I'm just going to go in until the hole appears to be wide enough that I can cut down a little further with this one.
So, with the Dremel on low speed--okay.
We made the hole a little bit rounder and wider.
Originally, I was going to use this bit to go all the way through but that hole is looking really, really good.
I don't think we're going to need to use this.
We can use--we can make a clasp just like this that doesn't--that even though this one won't go in, I'm going to make one like this that will fit in this hole and work just fine.
So, now, we're going to do the back just like we did the front with the exception of this hole.
We're just going to drill the hole and then--excuse me.
Hollow it out with the polish.